https://www.hollywoodloverugs.com/terms_security

Tweet
Sign In
Join
Cart (0 items - $0.00)
HomeShopAREA RUGSCOWHIDE RUGSFAUX FUR RUGSNATURAL RUGSSHAG RUGSSHEEPSKIN RUGSTHROW PILLOWSAboutGalleryBlogContact
Browse
HomeShopAboutGalleryBlogContact
Shop
AREA RUGSCOWHIDE RUGSFAUX FUR RUGSNATURAL RUGSSHAG RUGSSHEEPSKIN RUGSTHROW PILLOWS
Shopping Categories
AREA RUGSPolypropylene RugsCOWHIDE RUGSAnimal Print CowhidesDyed Cowhide LeatherNatural CalfskinNatural CowhidesFAUX FUR RUGSFake Bear RugsFaux Animal SkinsFaux Fur Area RugsFaux SheepskinNATURAL RUGSBamboo Rugs MatsJute Rugs MatsSeagrass Rugs MatsSisal Rugs MatsSHAG RUGSCotton Shag RugsFlokati RugsSHEEPSKIN RUGSDesigner Sheepskin RugsSheep Skin Area RugsSheepskin Pelt RugsTibetan LambswoolTHROW PILLOWSAnimal Print PillowsCowhide PIllowsFlokati PIllows
Privacy Policy
Hollywood Love Rugs
Privacy Statement
Due
to the fact that we gather certain types of information about our customers, we
feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the
acquisition and use of this information. By visiting
www.hollywoodloverugs.com
you are accepting the practices described in
this Privacy Statement.
Your information is safe and secure with
Hollywood Love Rugs
, and your privacy on the
Hollywood Love Rugs
website is a top priority.
Hollywood Love Rugs
does not sell, rent or exchange this
information for commercial purposes. The information we learn from you helps us provide you with the best possible service.
When you setup your account your information is considered private and will not
be shared with anyone outside of our company. On occasion you may receive
emails from us letting you know about upcoming sales, other company related
news or information.
We have strictly enforced procedures in place designed to ensure the privacy of your order and protect your personal information by processing all transactions through our secure Website.
Information collected from Registered Account Users is stored in our database and kept in secure locations under the custody and control of
Hollywood Love Rugs
and our e-commerce
hosting service. Registered accounts are password protected using the latest industry standards for the most effective security.
Hollywood Love Rugs
and our e-commerce hosting service uses every reasonable effort to protect your account information however we cannot guarantee with 100% certainty that such efforts will be successful.
The
web browser that you use allows for a small text file called a "Cookie" to be
saved to your computer’s hard drive. We only utilize cookies when you sign into
our web site to track the time you’ve spent on our site. These cookies do not
allow us to track your viewing of other web sites, they just let us know when
you sign in and sign out of our site.
Consistent
with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we
will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone
under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent.
You
can edit your account information at any time that you are logged into the website. You may do this in the checkout process when placing your order.
As
we make changes to our website we may also add to our privacy policy. This policy was last updated on February 23, 2011.
If
you have any questions about our website please don’t hesitate to contact us.
You can reach us via phone at
877 - Love Rug
or you can send us a message through our contact page.
Cart (0 items - $0.00)
Search Store
Advanced Search
Navigate
HomeShopAboutGalleryBlogContact
AREA RUGSCOWHIDE RUGSFAUX FUR RUGSNATURAL RUGSSHAG RUGSSHEEPSKIN RUGSTHROW PILLOWS
Site Options
Sitemap
Search
© 2020 Copyright Hollywood Love Rugs.
All Rights Reserved. We respect your privacy - Return policy - Sitemap
